iium.edu.my 2011-11-03

# Privacy Policy | International Islamic University Malaysia

This page explains our privacy policy which includes the use and protection of any information submitted by visitors. 

##  Your Policy

If you choose to register and transact using our website or send an e-mail which provides personally identifiable data, this data may be shared where necessary with other Faculty/Centres/Divisions so as to serve you in the most efficient and effective manner. An example might be in terms of resolving or addressing complaints that require escalation to other Faculty/Centres/Divisions.

##  Information Collected 

No personally identifiable information is gathered during the browsing of the IIUM website except for information given by you via e-mails, which is in a secure portion of the website.

##  Feedback 

We welcome all feedback and inquiries. In the case of any detailed information which the website may not be able to provide, your feedback/enquiry will be sent to the relevant Faculty/Centres/Divisions to better serve you.

##  Cookies

Certain websites generate cookies, which are collected by web-servers to enable them to recognise your future visits. The website uses only ‘non-persistent cookies’ or ‘per-session cookies’ which serve technical purposes like switching languages. These cookies do not permanently record data and are not stored on your computer’s hard drive. Once you close your browser, the cookie is deleted.

##  What Happens When I Link to Another Site? 

IIUM website contains links to other websites of both government and non-government organisations. This privacy policy applies only to our site and users should be aware that other sites linked by the website may have different privacy policies. We highly recommend that you read and understand the privacy statements of each site.

##  Changes to this Policy 

If this privacy policy changes in any way, it will be updated on this page. Regularly reviewing this page ensures you are updated on the information which is collected, how it is used and under what circumstances, if any, it is shared with other parties.

##  Queries or Complaints 

If you have any queries or complaints about this privacy policy or about the website, you can contact us via our Contact Us/Feedback section.
